( NARRATOR SPEAKING )
( WHIRRING )
WOMAN ON PA : All Umbrella staff must wear their identity tags at all times .
All radiation badges will be collected at 5 : 00 p.m. this afternoon .
Thank you ! God !
Some people .
Yeah .
( SNIFFING )
( DOGS BARKING )
( BEEPING )
May be I won 't show this time . Why not ?
Because I 'm busy .
( ALARM BEEPING )
It 's nothing . Fire drill .
What is that ?
Fire drill .
( ALARM CONTINUES BEEPING )
Shit ! Hey , what the hell is going on ?
Get the computers covered ! Move it !
Damn it , I 'm trying !
WOMAN : The experiments ! Move them !
Shouldn 't the doors open or something ?
WOMAN : It 's supposed to take us to the nearest floor .
Hello ? Hello ?
MAN : What 's happening ?
Line 's dead .
( BANGING ON DOOR )
What 's the problem ? WOMAN : The doors won 't open .
What about the ones at the back ?
Locked as well .
There 's no fire here ! No fire !
MAN : The code doesn 't work !
No fire !
What 's wrong with you ?
The door won 't open !
And this water isn 't going anywhere .
What ?
It 's a sealed room .
Help me with the door !
Oh , fuck the doors !
( YELLING )
( POUNDING )
MAN : We have to get out of here . What 's going on ?
Has this happened before ? We have to get out of here .
We have to get out of here ! Take it easy .
You take it easy !
Quiet !
( ELEVATOR CORDS WHINING )
Quiet .
What is that ?
( PEOPLE SCREAMING )
( SHUDDERS )
Oh , my God .
( ALL SCREAMING )
( GROANING )
Halon !
( ALL CLAMORING )
Stop it !
Stop it ! Stop !
( ALL COUGHING )
Help !
( GASPING )
( MAN GRUNTING )
Let me see .
We 're gonna have to get out of here .
We have to get out of this building !
Here , give me a hand .
That 's as far as they 'll go . They 're caught on something .
That 's wide enough . I can squeeze through . I 'll get help .
( GRUNTS )
I 'm stuck . You 're gonna have to push .
That 's it .
A bit more .
( CLANGING )
What was that ?
Oh , Christ ! It 's the brakes ! Get out !
I can 't move ! MAN : We have to get out of here !
( SCREAMING )
Push her out of the way !
Pull me back inside !
( SCREAMING )
( METAL RESONATING )
( SHOWER RUNNING )
( GASPS )
( BEEPING )
( GLASSES CLINKING )
( DOOR CLANKS OPEN )
Hello ?
( CLATTERING ) Hello ?
( BIRDS SQUAWKING )
( GASPS )
Who are you ? Move !
Don 't touch me ! Stop !
Get away from me ! Down !
( SCREAMS )
( GRUNTS )
What are you doing ? I 'm a cop !
I told you , I 'm a cop !
( DEVICE BEEPS )
You 're breaking my arm !
( GROANING )
Report .
Report now .
What ?
I want your report , soldier .
I don 't know what you 're talking about .
SOLDIER 1 : Sir , the house 's primary defenses have been activated .
She 's probably still suffering the side effects .
MATT : What are you doing with us ?
COMMANDER : What about the cop ?
SOLDIER 2 : Matthew Addison . I 'm not getting a match .
FEMALE SOLDIER : Who are you ?
I just transferred . They probably don 't even have me on file yet .
COMMANDER : The locals are inefficient . It 's possible .
FEMALE SOLDIER : Should I secure him here ?
No . We take him with us .
You can 't do this !
Blow me .
Hey !
Prep for entry to the Hive .
Power 's down .
So fix it .
I 'm on it .
Are you done yet ?
( CHUCKLES ) Jumpy .
( EXCLAIMS )
( POWER WHIRRING )
Stand clear !
You got a problem ?
How 's that door ?
It 's sealed shut .
Let me .
( CLICKS TONGUE )
( GRUNTING )
Jumpy ?
( MAN LAUGHING )
( GASPS )
Lie still . Lie still !
Watch this light . Follow it .
Now , how many fingers am I holding up ?
Three .
Good .
Now tell me your name .
I don 't know .
He 's fine . Memory loss , just like the other one .
Let 's open that door .
Listen to me .
I want to know who you people are
and I want to know what 's going on here .
Now !
COMMANDER : You and I have the same employer .
We all work for the Umbrella Corporation .
The mansion above us is an emergency entrance to the Hive .
You are security operatives placed there to protect that entrance .
What about this ?
Your marriage is a fake .
Just part of your cover to protect the secrecy of the Hive .
SPENCE : And what is the Hive ?
Show them .
Accessing schematic of the Hive .
COMMANDER : Raccoon City , nearest urban center .
The mansion where we found you
and through which we gained access to the train
which , in turn , brought us to the Hive .
The Hive itself is located underground
deep beneath the streets of Raccoon City .
A top-secret research facility
owned and operated by the Umbrella Corporation ,
the Hive houses over 500 technicians , scientists and support staff .
They live and work underground .
Their research is of the highest importance .
Its nature is classified .
Our position on the map is indicated by heat signature .
Why can 't I remember anything ?
The Hive has its own defense mechanisms , all computer-controlled .
A nerve gas was released into the house .
Primary effect of the gas ,
complete unconsciousness lasting anything up to four hours .
Secondary effects are varied , but can include acute memory loss .
For how long ? Subjective .
An hour , day , week .
So you 're saying this place was attacked ?
I 'm afraid things are a little more complicated than that .
Sir ! We 've breached the Hive .
J. D.
J. D. : Got it .
Halon content has dissipated .
( SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE )
Makes it easier to work underground , thinking there 's a view .
Looks like we 're taking the stairs .
COMMANDER : Status .
Red Queen is locked onto us .
She knows that we 're here .
Who 's the Red Queen ?
State-of-the-art artificial intelligence .
She is the computer that controls the Hive .
This is gonna slow us down .
Our route to the Queen takes us straight through these labs .
Rain , J. D. , see how bad the flooding is .
Kaplan , find us an alternate route .
What happened here ?
Five hours ago , Red Queen went homicidal .
Sealed the Hive and killed everyone down here .
Jesus .
When we realized what was happening ,
my team was dispatched to shut her down .
Why did she do it ?
That we don 't know .
But outside interference is a possibility .
Jesus !
Hey . You okay ?
Here . No .
I 'm fine . Please , come on .
It 's cold in here .
Are you ...
Do you remember anything from before this ?
No . Nothing before the train .
And you ?
No . Nothing .
KAPLAN : I found an alternate route , but it 's gonna cost us time .
We double back , cut through Dining Hall B , then we 're right on track .
Sir , no go . The whole level 's flooded .
COMMANDER : All right , we 're behind schedule .
So let 's move it .
Come on .
Poor bastards .
( KEYPAD BEEPING )
COMMANDER : Kaplan .
Dining Hall B.
That 's what it says on the map .
Maybe you 're reading it wrong .
Maybe the corporation 's keeping a few secrets down here .
Something you 're not supposed to see .
J. D. , you and Rain keep the prisoner here and secure the exit .
Sir , halon levels are nonexistent in this room .
I think the system malfunctioned .
All right . There may be survivors .
Give me a search line , but keep it tight .
Move it .
( LIQUID FLOWING )
( GASPS )
I said keep it tight .
Sorry .
I 'm not sure I want to remember what went on down here .
I don 't blame you .
What do they keep in these things ?
How do I know ?
What 's taking so long ?
Red Queen 's defenses are in place .
She 's making it difficult .
( BEEPING )
( DOOR OPENING )
Let 's pack it up .
You stay here .
KAPLAN : The lights are automated . Nothing to worry about .
Transmitter in position .
KAPLAN : Roger .
Running the bypass .
( BEEPING )
Checkmate .
Move up .
What is that ?
That 's what will shut the Queen down .
Delivers a massive electrical charge .
Scrambles the mainframe and forces it to reboot .
Kaplan .
Kaplan !
Some kind of dormant defense mechanism .
Opening the door tripped it .
COMMANDER : Put it back to sleep .
Working on it .
( ALARM WARBLING )
SPENCE : Would you open that door now , please ?
I 'm trying .
Hold your positions . Everyone stay calm .
What 's that ?
ALICE : Kaplan , quick !
SPENCE : We gotta get them out of there !
ALICE : Kaplan , you 've gotta hurry !
Come on !
Down ! Get down !
Look out ! Something 's killing them !
Jesus ! Come on , man .
Don 't do this to me !
Medic ! Medic !
( GROANING )
Open the door ! Open this door !
I am trying . Stay conscious .
You 're going into shock . Stay awake !
( INAUDIBLE ) I am almost there .
Sir ! It 's coming back !
Open the door ! I 'm trying !
Well , try harder !
It 's coming back !
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
Oh , God !
Just do it !
I 'm almost there .
Come on !
Shit ! Got it .
All right .
Let 's do it .
Do what ?
We have to complete the mission .
There is no way I 'm going down there .
Her defenses are down .
Déjà vu , anyone ?
( GASPS )
( SHUDDERING )
( GAS HISSING )
( WHIRRING )
Keep going .
Give me a hand .
Get out ! Get out ! You can 't be in here .
Don 't listen to anything she says .
She 's a holographic representation of the Red Queen .
You have to get out !
Modeled after the head programmer 's daughter .
She 'll try to deceive us , confuse us .
I wouldn 't advise this .
Disabling me will result in loss of primary power .
She 'll say anything to stop us from shutting her down .
I implore you .
Implore away .
Please ?
You 're all going to die down here .
( DETONATOR FIRES )
( SWITCHES CLANKING )
( LIQUID GURGLING )
( WHIRRING )
( CLANGING )
That pulse forces the circuit breaker
to shut down her mainframe for 30 seconds .
After that , if I don 't have her board , she can reboot .
They 're late .
( METALLIC SCRAPING )
I 'm on it .
( METAL CLANGING )
( CLANGING )
J. D. , we got a survivor !
It 's okay . We 're here to help .
You seem to be in some serious ...
( YELLS )
( SNARLING ) Get off of me !
Get off of me !
J. D. , get her off of me before I stab her ass !
( GRUNTS )
Are you okay ?
She bit me , man .
She took a chunk clean right out of me .
Stay down .
I 'm warning you , stay down !
She 's crazy .
( SNARLING )
Come any closer , and I 'll fire .
I mean it !
Damn you .
( SHRIEKING )
I shot her five times .
How was she still standing ?
Bitch isn 't standing now .
What was all the shooting ?
We found a survivor .
And you shot him ?
She was crazed . She bit me .
She 's gone . She 's gone !
That 's bullshit !
She fell right here , but she 's gone !
RAIN : Look , look at this .
There 's blood , but it 's not much .
Looks like it 's coagulated .
ALICE : Yeah .
It 's not possible .
J. D. : Why not ?
Because blood doesn 't do that till after you 're dead .
Can we go now ?
We 're not going anywhere till the rest of the team get here .
There 's no one else coming .
( METAL GRINDING )
What the fuck are you talking about ?
Wait .
Quiet .
( METAL GRINDING CONTINUES )
( SNARLING )
Fuck !
Don 't come any closer !
They 're behind us .
Jesus !
They 're everywhere .
They 're everywhere . They 're all around us .
( SNARLING )
I said stay back !
Why aren 't they dying ?
Watch the tank ! The tank !
Let 's go ! Hurry up !
Wait ! RAIN : Come on , let 's go !
Move !
Keep moving ! Come on !
ALICE : I can help you get the virus .
I have access to security codes ,
surveillance plans , the works .
Shit !
We lost the others !
Keep moving !
You waited ?
Didn 't know the code .
Come on , come on .
Shit ! Come on .
Come on . Hurry up .
Come on , man . Shit !
What 's taking so long ?
I 'm trying !
( GROWLING )
Come on .
Move ! What 's the code ? RAIN : Hurry up !
I 'm running out of ammo !
Zero , four , three , two ... No , fuck !
What ?
Zero , four , three ...
What is the code ?
Zero , four ,
zero , three , one , nine , six , five .
SPENCE : Got it ?
See how easy that was ?
Shit ! J. D. , no !
( SNARLING )
Grab my hand , man ! Come on !
Don 't let go !
( INAUDIBLE )
( SNARLING )
( SCREAMING )
J. D. ! Rain !
No !
( SCREAMING )
( CLANGING )
( GROWLING )
KAPLAN : Where are the bodies ? Where did they go ?
SPENCE : Fuck !
( POUNDING )
Whatever they are , there 's too many of them out there .
Whatever they are ? It 's pretty obvious what they are .
Lab coats , badges .
Those people used to work here !
All the people working here are dead .
Well , that isn 't stopping them from walking around .
Well , where did they come from ?
Why didn 't we see them on the way in ?
When you cut the power , you unlocked the doors .
You let them out .
( POUNDING CONTINUES )
We 're never gonna make it to the surface .
( DOOR CREAKS )
( FAINT CLICKING )
( GROWLING )
( SNARLING )
( YELLS )
COMMANDER : You are security operatives .
Security operatives placed there to protect that entrance .
( GASPS )
( GROWLING )
( GROWLS )
( YELLING )
( EXHALES )
Lisa .
( SNARLING )
I 've got one in the breech and an extra mag .
( POUNDING )
Lisa .
( WHEEZING )
( SNARLING )
ALICE : I can help you get the virus .
I have access to security codes ,
surveillance plans , the works .
But ?
But there 's gonna be a price .
Name it .
Who was she ?
My sister .
Corporations like Umbrella think they 're above the law .
But they 're not .
There are hundreds of thousands of us who think the same
all over the world .
Some of us provide information ,
others give their support .
Some take more direct action .
Like you .
If your friends had been a little more thorough ,
they would 've seen right through my false ID .
Then all the red flags would 've gone off ...
Quantico , NSA , VICAP , all the rest .
There 's no way I could 've infiltrated the Hive .
So you sent your sister .
We needed something concrete .
Anything to expose Umbrella to the press .
Proof of the research that was going on down here .
What kind of research ?
The illegal kind .
Genetic .
Viral .
My sister was going to smuggle out
a sample of the virus they were developing .
So how was she going to make it out of here ?
She had a contact within the Hive , someone I never met .
They had access to security codes ,
surveillance , everything she needed .
So why didn 't she make it ?
Maybe she trusted the wrong person .
Maybe they set her up .
Kept the virus for themselves .
Do you know how much the T-virus
would be worth on the open market ?
What , worth all this ?
Yeah .
To someone .
Don 't shoot ! Don 't shoot !
Close that door ! They 're right behind us !
Get off ! Get off !
Stop it !
Son of a bitch !
You okay ?
Yeah .
Right behind us . What about this door ?
They 're waiting out there too .
( POUNDING )
And that way ?
KAPLAN : It 's a dead end .
There 's no way out of the Queen 's chamber .
So we wait .
If someone doesn 't hear from you ,
they 'll send backup or something .
Right ?
What ? What 's wrong ?
We don 't have much time .
You know those blast doors we passed
on the way in from the mansion ?
They seal shut in just under an hour .
If we 're not out of here by then , we 're not getting out .
What are you talking about ?
They can 't just bury us alive down here .
Containing the incident is the only fail-safe plan they had
against possible contamination .
And you 're only telling us this now , when we 're trapped
half a mile underground ?
ALICE : We have to find a way out of this room .
What are you doing ?
Where are you taking those ?
I 'm turning her back on .
That is not a good idea .
She 'll know a way out of here .
That homicidal bitch killed my team .
That homicidal bitch may be our only way out of here .
Considering the way she 's been treated ,
I 'm sure she 'll be happy to help us out .
That circuit breaker you were talking about .
Can you bypass it ? Yeah .
So do it .
KAPLAN : All right , circuit breaker is disabled .
This time if I hit the switch ,
she won 't be able to shut down .
She 's gonna fry .
Kaplan ?
The initial charge must have damaged her boards .
RED QUEEN : Ah , there you are .
Things , I gather , have gone out of control .
Give me that fucking switch right now . I 'm gonna fry your ass .
I did warn you , didn 't I ?
Tell us what 's going on down here .
Research and development .
What about the T-virus ?
The T-virus was a major medical breakthrough
although it clearly also possessed
highly profitable military applications .
How does it explain those things out there ?
Even in death , the human body still remains active .
Hair and fingernails continue to grow .
New cells are produced
and the brain itself holds a small electrical charge
that takes months to dissipate .
The T-virus provides a massive jolt both to cellular growth
and to those trace electrical impulses .
Put quite simply it reanimates the body .
RAIN : It brings the dead back to life ?
Not fully .
The subjects have the simplest of motor functions .
Perhaps a little memory . Virtually no intelligence .
They are driven by the basest of impulses , the most basic of needs .
Which is ?
The need to feed .
How do you kill them ?
Severing the top of the spinal column
or massive trauma to the brain
are the most effective methods .
You mean shoot them in the head .
Why did you kill everybody down here ?
The T-virus escaped into the air conditioning system
and an uncontrolled pattern of infection began .
The virus is protean ,
changing from liquid to airborne to blood transmission
depending on its environment .
It 's almost impossible to kill .
I couldn 't allow it to escape from the Hive , so I took steps .
Steps .
You must understand .
Those who become infected , I can 't allow you to leave .
Whoa . We 're not infected .
Just one bite , one scratch from these creatures is sufficient
and then you become one of them .
A check of my systems indicates my main drive circuit breaker
has been disabled .
May I ask why ?
ALICE : Insurance . We need a way out of here .
If you refuse to help at any time , we flip the switch .
Understand ?
After you .
SPENCE : What the hell is this place ?
KAPLAN : The utility tunnels .
They run underneath the Hive for water , gas and power lines .
It 's been in here before .
Keep moving .
We 're going around in circles .
This is the route the computer gave us .
Why are you listening to her ?
Enough already !
We have no choice but to keep moving
' cause those things are right behind us .
God damn !
That mesh isn 't gonna hold . Keep moving .
Jesus Christ ! Hold it !
There 's too many of them !
Jesus ! Fuck !
( GRUNTS )
Up on the pipes . Up on the pipes !
Quickly , everyone !
Let 's go ! Come on ! There 's a way up !
Watch out ! Keep them back !
Go on up ! Move it !
( YELLS )
Shit . Okay .
( CREATURE GROWLING )
MATT : Get over here ! There 's too many of them !
Come on ! Go , go , go !
Go on !
Go ! Go ! I can manage !
MATT : Gotcha !
( SCREAMING )
( GUN FIRES )
( GROANING )
J. D.
( ROARING )
( RAIN SCREAMING )
( GUN FIRING )
Rain ? Rain .
What ?
We have to do something about your wounds .
I 'm fine .
I said I 'm fine .
( CREATURES CLAMORING )
You like that , don 't you ? Huh ?
You like the way it tastes , don 't you ?
Like the taste of that ?
She was right .
We 're all gonna die down here .
No . We 're getting out .
All of us .
( GRUNTING )
Kaplan , are you okay ?
( RIGGING CREAKING )
Kaplan !
No !
( SCREAMING )
ALICE : Oh , God !
( GRUNTS )
Hold on !
( GROWLING )
( SCREAMING )
Help him .
I can 't .
What are you waiting for ?
I can 't focus !
I can 't see !
( SNARLING )
( GUN FIRING )
ALICE : Kaplan , go up !
SPENCE : Get up there !
You almost got it . Keep going !
Come on ! Come on !
MATT : You can do it !
ALICE : You got it !
Okay , Kaplan . MAN : Just stay there !
Hold on . We 're gonna come get you .
Cut this wire and throw it to him .
Then we can go get him .
Hold on !
That 's lucky .
I want you to go .
We 're not leaving you , Kaplan .
Yes , you are .
- No . - KAPLAN : You can 't kill all of them .
And I 'm not going anywhere .
I want you to go . Now !
Please .
Just do it .
Just do it now !
Please .
Go !
( GUN FIRES )
You 're gonna have to work for your meal !
( GROANING )
Come on .
Give me your arm . Up over my shoulder .
Ready ? There we go .
( VOMITING )
( CREATURE EXHALING )
When I get out of here
I think I 'm gonna get laid .
( CHUCKLES ) Yeah . You might want to clean up a little bit first .
Hey , wait .
( INDISTINCT WHISPERING )
Are you okay ?
( INDISTINCT CHATTERING )
ALICE : Blue for the virus . Green for the antivirus .
Blue for the virus . Green for the antivirus .
There 's a cure .
What are you talking about ?
The process can be reversed .
There 's a cure !
You 're gonna be okay !
I was beginning to worry .
This is where they kept the T-virus .
How do you know all this ?
Because I was gonna steal it .
I was your sister 's contact .
You betrayed her . I don 't know .
You caused all of this . I can 't remember .
The truth .
I don 't remember the truth .
( GRUNTING )
I don 't understand !
It 's gone .
It 's not there .
I can 't .
I just can 't .
It 's over . No .
ALICE : I can help you get the virus .
I have access to security codes ,
surveillance plans , the works .
But there 's gonna be a price .
Name it .
You have to guarantee me that you will bring this corporation down .
Spence ?
( VIAL SMASHING )
Thank you .
Spence ?
( CLICKING TONGUE )
We can still make it out of here .
Come with me .
We can have everything we 've ever wanted .
Money 's out there waiting .
You wouldn 't believe how much .
Is that how you thought all my dreams were gonna come true ?
Please . I wouldn 't want to shoot you .
Might need the bullets .
Back off .
I won 't take any part in this .
Okay , but you can 't just wash your hands of this .
We work for the same company . You knew what they did .
I was trying to stop them .
( SCOFFING ) You really believe that
people like him will ever change anything ?
Nothing ever changes .
Where is the antivirus ?
It 's on the train
where you found me .
Couldn 't have been standing more than three feet from it .
I so nearly made it out .
Didn 't realize that bitch of a computer
had defense systems outside the Hive .
In or out ?
I don 't know what we had but it 's over .
( SCREAMING )
Back ...
The fuck off .
I 'm missing you already .
Your boyfriend 's a real asshole .
MATT : He shot the locking mechanism out .
I can 't believe that son of a bitch is gonna get away with this .
RED QUEEN : I don 't think so .
I 've been a bad , bad girl .
( CHUCKLES )
( RUMBLING )
( CLANGING )
( HISSING )
Oh , my God .
( SCREAMING )
( CREATURE CHOMPING )
( ROARING )
What the fuck is that ?
RED QUEEN : One of the Hive 's early experiments
produced by injecting the T-virus directly into living tissue .
The results were unstable .
Now that it has fed on fresh DNA , it will mutate ...
( ROARING )
becoming a stronger , faster hunter .
Great .
If you knew it was loose , why didn 't you warn us ?
' Cause she was saving it for us .
Isn 't that right ?
I didn 't think any of you would make it this far .
Not without infection .
Why didn 't you tell us about the antivirus ?
This long after infection there 's no guarantee it would work .
But there 's a chance , right ?
I don 't deal in chance .
Fuck it .
( BEEPING )
No pressure , guys .
You require the four-digit access code .
I can give you the code , but first you must do something for me .
What do you want ?
One of your group is infected .
I require her life for the code .
The antivirus is right there on the platform .
It 's right there !
I 'm sorry .
It 's a risk I cannot take .
She 's right . It 's the only way .
You 're gonna have to kill me .
No .
Otherwise we all die down here .
( BANGING )
( ROARING )
The glass is reinforced but it won 't hold forever .
Do it . No .
Get up . RAIN : Just do it .
Rain , please get up . Do it !
You don 't have long to decide .
Get up , please .
You have no choice . Kill her .
Kill her now . You don 't have any choice .
( ROARING )
Just do it now !
ALICE : I can 't !
RAIN : Please . Do it .
Kill her . Just do it .
Kill her now !
( SCREAMING )
Kill her !
( WHIRRING )
( BANGING )
Kaplan ?
( WHIMPERS )
The bitch wouldn 't open the door , so I had to fry her .
Move .
( ROARING )
What the fuck was that ?
ALICE : It 's a long story .
Start it up .
I 'll get the virus .
( WHIRRING )
( GASPS )
( SCREECHING )
( HOWLING )
I 'm missing you already .
( PANEL BEEPING )
Okay , we 're in business .
Full power .
We 're leaving !
I don 't want to be one of those things
walking around without a soul .
You won 't .
When the time comes
you 'll take care of it .
No one else is gonna die .
Okay ?
( INJECTOR CLICKING )
RAIN : Here .
ALICE : Rain ?
Rain ?
( SHUDDERING )
( GASPS )
I 'm not dead yet .
I think I 'll have that back .
I could kiss you , you bitch .
What 's going on back there ?
Get us the fuck out of here !
Any faster , we 'll come off the rails !
( ROARING )
( SCREAMING )
( FOOTSTEPS BANGING ON ROOF )
( POUNDING )
( ROARING )
( GRUNTING )
( YELLING )
( HISSING )
( SCREAMING )
( SHRIEKING )
Open the doors !
( SNARLING )
ALICE : Open the doors !
Now !
( SCREECHING )
( ALICE WHIMPERING )
I failed all of them .
I failed .
Listen to me .
There is nothing else you could 've done .
The corporation 's guilty here , not you .
And we finally have the proof .
That way Umbrella can 't get ...
Get away with this .
( GROANS )
What is it ?
( GROANING )
You 're infected , but you 're gonna be okay .
I 'm not losing you .
Help !
Help him . What are you doing ?
( GRUNTING )
Matt !
He 's mutating .
( GROANING )
I want him in the Nemesis Program .
Get off !
MATT : What 's happening ?
Matt !
MAN : I want her quarantined .
Close observation and a full series of blood tests .
Let 's see if she 's infected .
Take her to the Raccoon City facility .
Then assemble the team .
We 're reopening the Hive .
I want to know what went on down there .
Just do it .
( SCREAMING )
( GRUNTING )
( PIERCING ECHO )
( YELLING )
( MUFFLED ) Who 's in there ?
Let me out !
Who 's in there ?
( ELECTRICAL CRACKLING )
( LOCK WHIRRING OPEN )
( GASPS )
( MY PLAGUE [ NEW ABUSE MIX ] PLAYING )
♪ I 'm in conniptions for the final act you came here for ♪
♪ The one derivative you manage is the one I abhor ♪
♪ I need a minute to eliminate for everyone the everyday abusive things you have done ♪
♪ Your impossible ego fuck is like a megalomaniacal tab on my tongue ♪
♪ And if you touch me I will rip you apart ♪
♪ I 'll reach in and take a bite out of that shit you call a heart ♪
♪ I know why you blame me ♪
♪ I know why you blame yourself ♪
♪ I know why you plague me ♪
♪ I know why you plague yourself ♪
♪ I 'm turning it around like a knife on the shelf ♪
♪ I want to understand why but I 'm learning myself ♪
♪ I haven 't seen a lotta reasons to stop it ♪
♪ I can 't just drop it ♪
♪ I 'm just a bastard But at least I admit it At least I admit it ♪
♪ I know why you blame me ♪
♪ I know why you blame yourself ♪
♪ I know why you plague me ♪
♪ I know why you plague yourself ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I know why you blame me ♪
♪ I know why you blame yourself ♪
♪ I know why you plague me ♪
♪ I know why you plague yourself ♪
♪ I know why you blame me ♪
♪ I know why you blame yourself ♪
♪ I know why you blame yourself ! ♪
(
SOMETHING PLAYING )
♪ Something told me to tell you ♪
♪ Not to tell me what to do ♪
♪ I am what I fucking am ♪
♪ Many have tried to change this man ♪
♪ Life 's always been an uphill fight ♪
♪ Some things I do you may not like ♪
♪ Something told me to tell you ♪
♪ Don 't give it to me ♪
♪ Why do you do the shit you do ? ♪
♪ I 'm doing just what I do ♪
♪ No , not what I want to do But what I 've got to do ♪
♪ We 're through ♪
♪ Life 's always been an uphill fight ♪
♪ Some things I do you may not like ♪
♪ Something told me to tell you ♪
♪ Don 't give it to me ♪
♪ Not to tell me what to do ♪
♪ I am what I fucking am ♪
♪ Many have tried to change this man ♪
♪ Life 's always been an uphill fight ♪
♪ Some things I do you may not like ♪
♪ Something told me to tell you ♪
♪ Don 't give it to me ♪
♪ I 'm sick of this shit I 'm sick of this shit ♪
♪ I 'm sick of this shit ♪
( INVISIBLE WOUNDS PLAYING )
♪ Unconscious Or am I conscious ? ♪
♪ Fell from the sky like a star ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel as though I 'm frozen in heaven ♪
RAIN : When I get out of here , think I 'm gonna get laid .
♪ And I saw ♪
♪ My own voice ♪
♪ In the dark ♪
♪ And loneliness ♪
♪ And I saw ♪
♪ My own voice ♪
♪ Like a spark ♪
♪ Frozen in heaven ♪
♪ Dark ♪ ♪ Dark bodies floating in darkness ♪
♪ Dark bodies floating in darkness ♪